=Just Fiancée= =Episode 9=
= مخطوبون فقط = = الحلقة 9 =
You are nothing like Gu Manman!
أنت لست مثل Gu Manman!
He will notice it at first sight!
سوف يلاحظ ذلك من النظرة الأولى!
I knew it!
كنت أعرف!
I am nothing to you all.
أنا لا شيء لكم جميعا.
Don't be mad.
لا تغضب.
What are you thinking about?
بم تفكر؟
My father.
والدي.
Though he is only my adoptive father,
على الرغم من أنه والدي بالتبني فقط ،
he loved me very much.
لقد أحبني كثيرا.
When I was little and I got sick,
عندما كنت صغيرا ومرضت ،
he would carry me on his back
سيحملني على ظهره
and walked dozens of kilometers
وسار عشرات الكيلومترات
to the town to see a doctor.
إلى المدينة لرؤية الطبيب.
But
ولكن
I can't be with him anymore.
لا أستطيع أن أكون معه بعد الآن.
The only one person in this world
الشخص الوحيد في هذا العالم
that loved me
الذي أحبني
has left me.
لقد تركني.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
You have me.
لديك لي.
No matter what problems you face,
بغض النظر عن المشاكل التي تواجهها ،
I will help you deal with them.
سوف أساعدك في التعامل معهم.
I'm hungry now.
أنا جائع الآن.
I will ask Aunt Zhang
سأطلب العمة تشانغ
to cook noodles for you.
لطهي المعكرونة لك.
When I was little,
عندما كنت صغيرا،
my dad would make egg noodles for me.
كان والدي يصنع لي نودلز البيض.
Then I will ask Aunt Zhang to add an egg, too?
ثم سأطلب من العمة تشانغ أن تضيف بيضة أيضًا؟
You,
أنت،
all you know is how to yell at others!
كل ما تعرفه هو كيف تصرخ على الآخرين!
What is it?
ما هذا؟
How many eggs are left?
كم عدد البيض المتبقي؟
It's because the eggs are of poor quality.
ذلك لأن البيض رديء الجودة.
I'll ask Aunt Zhang to buy
سأطلب من العمة تشانغ أن تشتريها
some good ones tomorrow.
بعض الطيبين غدا.
Then will I be able to have
ثم سأكون قادرة على الحصول عليها
egg noodles tonight?
نودلز البيض الليلة؟
Of course! I will crack another egg for you.
بالطبع!  سأكسر بيضة أخرى من أجلك.
Give it here.
أعطها هنا.
Let me teach you how to crack an egg!
اسمحوا لي أن أعلمك كيفية كسر بيضة!
Up next, I will show you
بعد ذلك ، سأريك
my family's traditional method
الطريقة التقليدية لعائلتي
of cracking an egg.
من تكسير بيضة.
Who was the one
من كان
that said she would teach me?
التي قالت أنها ستعلمني؟
People make mistakes.
الناس يخطئون.
Are you aware that
هل تدرك ذلك
mistakes
اخطاء
lead to punishment?
يؤدي إلى العقوبة؟
Who is it?
من هذا؟
Get out of my way.
ابتعد عن طريقي.
Why are you people in my house?
لماذا أنتم أيها الناس في بيتي؟
Who are you?
من أنت؟
Get out!
اخرج!
Why are you at my home?
لماذا انت في بيتي؟
If you don't get out, I will call the police!
إذا لم تخرج ، سأتصل بالشرطة!
I'll call the police for you.
سأتصل بالشرطة من أجلك.
Don't do that.
لا تفعل ذلك.
The girl is drunk.
الفتاة في حالة سكر.
Let's find out what's going on first.
دعنا نتعرف على ما يحدث أولاً.
Miss,
يغيب،
are you OK?
هل أنت بخير؟
Why did you come to our home?
لماذا أتيت إلى منزلنا؟
Miss Gu?
ملكة جمال جو؟
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
Excuse me.
اعذرني.
I drank too much and got lost.
شربت كثيرا واهت.
I'll leave now.
سأغادر الآن.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Mr. Gu.
السيد.  قو.
I saw Miss Gu just now.
لقد رأيت الآنسة جو للتو.
What?
ماذا؟
Good job!
أحسنت!
Come back first.
عد أولا.
OK.
نعم.
Oh yeah, Qiao Mai.
أوه نعم ، كياو ماي.
Something doesn't feel right
شيء ما ليس على ما يرام
about that woman.
عن تلك المرأة.
I have never seen her
انا لم ارها ابدا
around this area before.
حول هذه المنطقة من قبل.
You've been saying that
كنت تقول ذلك
for more than an hour.
لأكثر من ساعة.
It's so boring.
انها مملة جدا.
I'm serious.
أنا جادة.
I really think something is wrong.
أنا حقا أعتقد أن هناك خطأ ما.
Don't you think so too?
ألا تعتقد ذلك أيضًا؟
Qiao Mai!
تشياو ماي!
Aren't you gonna finish your food?
ألا تنهي طعامك؟
I feel sleepy.
أشعر بالنعاس.
Let's go upstairs, all right?
دعنا نذهب للأعلى ، حسناً؟
You'll catch a cold sleeping here.
ستصاب بنزلة برد تنام هنا.
I just want to take a nap.
أنا فقط أريد أن آخذ قيلولة.